rowleycompany.com 2016-10-07

# Security & Privacy Policy | Rowley

  * [Home](http://www.rowleycompany.com/) /
  * Security & Privacy Policy

Rowley Company (Rowley) operates its website in accordance with the following privacy policy. By using Rowley's website, you consent to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

Please note that this policy only affects information gathered through this website. If Rowley already includes your information in its email list or databases, or if it adds your information to its email list or databases through its other activities, this information and Rowley's use of it will not be affected by this policy.

 **Information Collected**

You can have access to our website without providing any personally identifying information. Rowley only collects personally identifying information when you voluntarily submit it, such as when you e-mail comments to the website, shop, make a purchase, or request information. This information is used for internal purposes only and helps us determine how we can improve the website to meet your needs. You must obtain a login and password to shop our products due to the nature of our business.

Like many other commercial websites, we collect non-personally identifiable information from you passively by tracking your activity on our site, often through the use of cookies. That information includes, among other things, the type of computer operating system and Internet browser that are being used and the domain name of your Internet service provider. This information helps us to better interact with visitors to our site.

 **Use of Personal Information**

Rowley uses your personal information only for the following:

  * For the purpose for which it was provided. If you provide information for a specific purpose, it will be used for that purpose. For example, if you request information about Rowley, Rowley will utilize your name and address to send you that information.
  * To inform you about Rowley products, events, services, and opportunities. Rowley would like to be able to contact you and send you information about its activities, products, services, and events in which Rowley hopes you might be interested.
  * To contact you about the website to determine ways in which it may be improved.
  * To gain information about how we may better serve you.

You always have the choice not to receive marketing information. At any time, you can choose to unsubscribe from receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email you no longer wish to receive.

 **Release of Information to Third Parties**

Rowley does not release or share your personally identifying information to third parties unless you have given us permission to do so or unless such release is required to comply with the law or to protect the rights of Rowley website users.

 **Security**

Rowley receives your personal and credit card information using the latest secure socket layering (SSL) technology which prevents disclosure of your information to third parties. Click on the Secure Site Seal on the purchase page to verify the validity of our VeriSign SSL Certificate. Information exchanged with any address beginning with https is encrypted using SSL before transmission.

 **Links to Other Sites**

Rowley is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such any websites to which it provides links.

 **Changes to Privacy Policy**

Rowley reserves the right to modify our policy as needed.

 **Contacting the Site**

If you have any questions or comments about this privacy policy, please contact Rowley via email at [info@Rowleycompany.com](mailto:info@Rowleycompany.com).
